aglasem.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy – aglasem.com

We are very delighted that you have shown interest in our enterprise. Data protection is of a particularly high priority for the management of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. (hereinafter “AglaSem”) The use of the Internet pages of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. is possible without any indication of personal data; however, if a data subject wants to use special enterprise services via our website, processing of personal data could become necessary. 

This Privacy Policy applies to the website https://www.aglasem.com (hereinafter “Website”) and related services offered on the Website, including off-site services (“Services”).

AglaSem (“we” or “us”) can modify this Privacy Policy, and if we make material changes to it, we will provide notice through our Services, or by other means, to provide you the opportunity to review the changes before they become effective. If you object to any changes, you may close your account.

You acknowledge that your continued use of our Services after we publish or send a notice about our changes to this Privacy Policy means that the collection, use and sharing of your personal data is subject to the updated Privacy Policy.

The processing of personal data, such as the name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number of a data subject accessing the Website in India shall always be in line with the Information Technology Act, 2000, including all amendments, in India; the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for data subjects located in the Designated Countries such as European Union (EU), European Economic Area (EEA), and Switzerland, and in accordance with the country-specific data protection regulations applicable to data subjects accessing the Website in countries other than India and Designated Countries. By means of this data protection declaration, AglaSem would like to inform the general public of the nature, scope, and purpose of the personal data we collect, use and process. Furthermore, data subjects are informed, by means of this data protection declaration, of the rights to which they are entitled.

As the controller and processor, AglaSem has implemented numerous technical and organizational measures to ensure the most complete protection of personal data processed through this Website. However, Internet-based data transmissions may in principle have security gaps, so absolute protection may not be guaranteed. For this reason, every data subject is free to transfer personal data to us via alternative means, e.g. by telephone.

#### 1\. Definitions

The data protection declaration of AglaSem is based on the terms used by the European legislator for the adoption of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and in compliance with the Information Technology Act, 2000. Our data protection declaration should be legible and understandable for the general public, as well as our customers and business partners. To ensure this, we would like to first explain the terminology used.

In this data protection declaration, we use, inter alia, the following terms:

**a) Personal data**  
Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (“data subject”). An identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.

**b) Data subject**

Data subject is any identified or identifiable natural person, whose personal data is processed by the controller responsible for the processing.

**c) Processing**  
Processing is any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

**d) Restriction of processing**  
Restriction of processing is the marking of stored personal data with the aim of limiting their processing in the future.

**e) Profiling**  
Profiling means any form of automated processing of personal data consisting of the use of personal data to evaluate certain personal aspects relating to a natural person, in particular to analyse or predict aspects concerning that natural person’s performance at work, economic situation, health, personal preferences, interests, reliability, behaviour, location or movements.

**f) Pseudonymisation**  
Pseudonymisation is the processing of personal data in such a manner that the personal data can no longer be attributed to a specific data subject without the use of additional information, provided that such additional information is kept separately and is subject to technical and organisational measures to ensure that the personal data are not attributed to an identified or identifiable natural person.

**g) Controller or controller responsible for the processing**  
Controller or controller responsible for the processing is the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data; where the purposes and means of such processing are determined by Union or Member State law, the controller or the specific criteria for its nomination may be provided for by Union or Member State law.

**h) Processor**  
Processor is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller.

**i) Recipient**  
Recipient is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or another body, to which the personal data are disclosed, whether a third party or not. However, public authorities which may receive personal data in the framework of a particular inquiry in accordance with Union or Member State law shall not be regarded as recipients; the processing of those data by those public authorities shall be in compliance with the applicable data protection rules according to the purposes of the processing.

**j) Third party**  
Third party is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or body other than the data subject, controller, processor and persons who, under the direct authority of the controller or processor, are authorised to process personal data.

**k) Consent**  
Consent of the data subject is any freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous indication of the data subject’s wishes by which he or she, by a statement or by a clear affirmative action, signifies agreement to the processing of personal data relating to him or her.

#### 2\. Name and Address of the controller

Controller for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), other data protection laws applicable in Designated Countries and other provisions related to data protection is:

AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd.  
503, Park Centra, Sector 30, Gurgaon, India – 122001  
Phone: 01244717818  
Email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
Website: www.aglasem.com

#### 3\. Cookies

The Internet pages of AglaSem use cookies. Cookies are text files that are stored in a computer system via an Internet browser.

Many Internet sites and servers use cookies. Many cookies contain a so-called cookie ID. A cookie ID is a unique identifier of the cookie. It consists of a character string through which Internet pages and servers can be assigned to the specific Internet browser in which the cookie was stored. This allows visited Internet sites and servers to differentiate the individual browser of the data subject from other Internet browsers that contain other cookies. A specific Internet browser can be recognized and identified using the unique cookie ID.

Through the use of cookies, the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. can provide the users of this Website with more user-friendly services that would not be possible without the cookie setting.

By means of a cookie, the information and offers on our website can be optimized with the user in mind. Cookies allow us, as previously mentioned, to recognize our website users. The purpose of this recognition is to make it easier for users to utilize our website. The website user that uses cookies, e.g. does not have to enter access data each time the website is accessed, because this is taken over by the website, and the cookie is thus stored on the user’s computer system.  
The data subject may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies through our website by means of a corresponding setting of the Internet browser used, and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. If the data subject deactivates the setting of cookies in the Internet browser used, not all functions of our website may be entirely usable.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

#### 4\. Collection of general data and information

The Website of AglaSem collects a series of general data and information when a data subject accesses or automated system calls up the Website. This general data and information are stored in the server log files. Collected information may inlcude (1) the browser types and versions used, (2) the operating system used by the accessing system, (3) the website from which an accessing system reaches our website (so-called referrers), (4) the sub-websites, (5) the date and time of access to the Internet site, (6) an Internet protocol address (IP address), (7) the Internet service provider of the accessing system, and (8) any other similar data and information that may be used in the event of attacks on our information technology systems.

When using these general data and information, AglaSem does not collect any personal data or draw any conclusions about the data subject. Rather, this information is non-personal data which is needed to (1) deliver the content of our website correctly, (2) optimize the content of our website as well as its advertisement, (3) ensure the long-term viability of our information technology systems and website technology, and (4) provide law enforcement authorities with the information necessary for criminal prosecution in case of a cyber-attack. Therefore, AglaSem analyzes anonymously collected data and information statistically, with the aim of increasing the data protection and data security of our enterprise, and to ensure an optimal level of protection for the personal data we process. The anonymous data of the server log files are stored separately from all personal data provided by a data subject.

#### 5\. Registration on our website

The data subject has the possibility to register on the website of the controller with the indication of personal data. Which personal data are transmitted to the controller is determined by the respective input mask used for the registration which could include the name, address, mobile number, address etc.. The personal data entered by the data subject are collected and stored exclusively for internal use by the controller, and for his own purposes. The controller may request transfer to one or more processors that also uses personal data for an internal purpose which is attributable to the controller.

By registering on the website of the controller, the IP address—assigned by the Internet service provider (ISP) and used by the data subject—date, and time of the registration are also stored. The storage of this data takes place against the background that this is the only way to prevent the misuse of our services, and, if necessary, to make it possible to investigate committed offenses. Insofar, the storage of this data is necessary to secure the controller. This data is not passed on to third parties unless there is a statutory obligation to pass on the data, or if the transfer serves the aim of criminal prosecution.

The registration of the data subject, with the voluntary indication of personal data, is intended to enable the controller to offer the data subject contents or services that may only be offered to registered users due to the nature of the matter in question. Registered persons are free to change the personal data specified during the registration at any time, or to have them completely deleted from the data stock of the controller.

The data controller shall, at any time, provide information upon request to each data subject as to what personal data are stored about the data subject. In addition, the data controller shall correct or erase personal data at the request or indication of the data subject, insofar as there are no statutory storage obligations. The entirety of the controller’s employees are available to the data subject in this respect as contact persons.

#### 6\. Subscription to our newsletters

On the website of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd., users are given the opportunity to subscribe to our enterprise’s newsletter. The input mask used for this purpose determines what personal data are transmitted, as well as when the newsletter is ordered from the controller.

The AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. informs its customers and business partners regularly by means of a newsletter about enterprise offers. The enterprise’s newsletter may only be received by the data subject if (1) the data subject has a valid e-mail address and (2) the data subject registers for the newsletter shipping. A confirmation e-mail will be sent to the e-mail address registered by a data subject for the first time for newsletter shipping, for legal reasons, in the double opt-in procedure. This confirmation e-mail is used to prove whether the owner of the e-mail address as the data subject is authorized to receive the newsletter.

During the registration for the newsletter, we also store the IP address of the computer system assigned by the Internet service provider (ISP) and used by the data subject at the time of the registration, as well as the date and time of the registration. The collection of this data is necessary in order to understand the (possible) misuse of the e-mail address of a data subject at a later date, and it therefore serves the aim of the legal protection of the controller.

The personal data collected as part of a registration for the newsletter will only be used to send our newsletter. In addition, subscribers to the newsletter may be informed by e-mail, as long as this is necessary for the operation of the newsletter service or a registration in question, as this could be the case in the event of modifications to the newsletter offer, or in the event of a change in technical circumstances. There will be no transfer of personal data collected by the newsletter service to third parties. The subscription to our newsletter may be terminated by the data subject at any time. The consent to the storage of personal data, which the data subject has given for shipping the newsletter, may be revoked at any time. For the purpose of revocation of consent, a corresponding link is found in each newsletter. It is also possible to unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time directly on the website of the controller, or to communicate this to the controller in a different way.

#### 7\. Newsletter-Tracking

The newsletter of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. contains so-called tracking pixels. A tracking pixel is a miniature graphic embedded in such e-mails, which are sent in HTML format to enable log file recording and analysis. This allows a statistical analysis of the success or failure of online marketing campaigns. Based on the embedded tracking pixel, the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. may see if and when an e-mail was opened by a data subject, and which links in the e-mail were called up by data subjects.

Such personal data collected in the tracking pixels contained in the newsletters are stored and analyzed by the controller in order to optimize the shipping of the newsletter, as well as to adapt the content of future newsletters even better to the interests of the data subject. These personal data will not be passed on to third parties. Data subjects are at any time entitled to revoke the respective separate declaration of consent issued by means of the double-opt-in procedure. After a revocation, these personal data will be deleted by the controller. The AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. automatically regards a withdrawal from the receipt of the newsletter as a revocation.

#### 8\. Contact possibility via the website

The website of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. contains information that enables a quick electronic contact to our enterprise, as well as direct communication with us, which also includes a general address of the so-called electronic mail (e-mail address). If a data subject contacts the controller by e-mail or via a contact form, the personal data transmitted by the data subject are automatically stored. Such personal data transmitted on a voluntary basis by a data subject to the data controller are stored for the purpose of processing or contacting the data subject. There is no transfer of this personal data to third parties.

#### 9\. Posting and Uploading

We collect personal data from you when you provide, post or upload it to our Services, such as when you fill out an examination/admission form, respond to a survey, take tests or submit a paper. You don’t have to post or upload personal data; though if you don’t, it may limit your ability to grow and engage with your network over our Services.

#### 10\. Partners

We receive personal data about you when you use the services of our partners, such as some schools, universities, colleges and applicant tracking systems.

#### 11\. Lawful Bases for Processing

We will only collect and process personal data about you where we have lawful bases. Lawful bases include consent (where you have given consent) and contract (where processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you (e.g. to deliver the Services you have requested).

Where we rely on your consent to process personal data, you have the right to withdraw or decline your consent at any time. If you have any questions about the lawful bases upon which we collect and use your personal data, please contact our Data Protection Officer here.

#### 11\. Use of the Data Collected

Information about upcoming exams, deadlines. Our Services allow you to stay informed about notes, solutions, sample papers, olympiads, talent search examinations at schools, entrance exams and admissions updates, preparation, query solving news pertaining to admissions in schools, colleges, universities, professional courses, teacher eligibility test, railways recruitment updates and preparation, guidance network of students and job seeker community forum, events and ideas regarding professional topics you care about, and from professionals you respect. Our Services also allow you to improve your professional skills, or learn new ones. We use the data we have about you (e.g., data you provide, data we collect from your engagement with our Services and inferences we make from the data we have about you), to recommend relevant content and conversations on our Services, suggest skills you may have to add to your profile and skills that you might need to pursue your next opportunity. So, if you let us know that you are interested in a new skill (e.g., by watching a learning video), we will use this information to personalize content in your feed, suggest that you follow certain members on our site, or watch related learning content to help you towards that new skill. 

**Career**  
Our Services allow you to explore careers, evaluate educational opportunities, and seek out, and be found for, career opportunities. Your We will use your data to recommend jobs to you and you to recruiters. We may use automated systems to profile and provide recommendations to help make our Services more relevant to our Members, Visitors and customers. Keeping your profile accurate and up-to-date may help you better connect to others and to opportunities through our Services.

**Marketing**  
We use data and content about data subjects for invitations and communications promoting information about new courses, exams, online tests, engagement and our Services.

**Aggregate Information**  
We will also use Personal Information and non-personally identifiable information and other information (including information from online and offline third party sources) to create aggregated data for analytical and other purposes. We use this information to do internal research on your demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve You. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, We only use this data in aggregate form. 

**Non-personally identifiable information**  
We may freely use Non Personally Identifiable Information in connection with the Services offered through Impactify, including: to administer the Services being offered thereunder, to understand how well our Service is working, to market the Services and other products and services, to develop aggregate, statistical information on usage of the Service and to generally improve the Service.

#### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We may also use your Personal Information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as new services, rewards and promotions. The following are some circumstances under which we would share your Information with from time-to-time:

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We do not disclose your email address, telephone number and mailing address to any third party for marketing purposes. Except as otherwise provided under this Privacy Policy, we will disclose your Personal Information to third parties only in the following limited circumstances:

(i) if you use the Service through AglaSem, we may disclose your Personal Information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with us under confidentiality agreements. These entities may use your Personal Information for performing services, administering promotions, analyzing data and usage of the Service through AglaSem, processing credit card payments, operating the Service or providing support and maintenance services for the same, or providing customer service. 

(ii) when we have your consent to otherwise share the information.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may disclose other Non-Personally Identifiable Information to third party advertisers and advertising agencies, partners, and other parties in order for us and such third parties to analyze (a) the performance of, to operate and improve the Services offered through Impactify, and (b) the behavior of data subjects and to target offers to data subjects depending upon their requirements. We may also disclose, use or publish this information for promoting the Services offered under AglaSem. These third parties are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses. 

Aggregate Information: Because the aggregate information we collect does not specifically identify you, it may be shared with any number of parties. For example, we may disclose anonymous, aggregated information to third parties such as potential business partners, end users, service providers, advertisers, and funding sources, in order to describe our business and operations.

Network Operators: Use of the Service provided through AglaSem may involve use of the services of third party telecommunications carriers and service providers (such as the services of the carrier that provides cell phone or internet service to you). Such carriers and service providers are not our contractors, and any information that a carrier collects in connection with your use of the Service provided through AglaSem is not “Personal Information” and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the acts or omissions of telecommunications carriers or service providers.

Additional Disclosures: Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, We reserve the right to use or disclose Personal Information and any other information we collect in connection with the Service offered through AglaSem (a) to any successor to our business, including as a result of any merger, acquisition, asset sale or similar transaction, whose privacy practices are substantially similar to ours(b) to any corporate affiliate of ours whose privacy practices are substantially similar to ours, (c) to any law enforcement, judicial authority, governmental or regulatory authority, to the extent required by law or legal process, or (d) if in our reasonable discretion, such use or disclosure is necessary to enforce or protect our legal rights or to protect third parties. 

**Other Websites**

AglaSem may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website/application over which we have no control and will bear no responsibility. Often these websites/applications require you to enter your personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such websites/application as their policies may differ from ours. You agree that we shall not be liable for any breach of your privacy of personal information or loss incurred by your use of these websites /application. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected by us.

**Routine erasure and blocking of personal data**  
The data controller shall process and store the personal data of the data subject only for the period necessary to achieve the purpose of storage, or as far as this is granted by the European legislator or other legislators in laws or regulations to which the controller is subject to.

If the storage purpose is not applicable, or if a storage period prescribed by the European legislator or another competent legislator expires, the personal data are routinely blocked or erased in accordance with legal requirements.

#### 10\. Rights of the data subject

**a) Right of confirmation**  
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller the confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning him or her are being processed. If a data subject wishes to avail himself of this right of confirmation, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.

**b) Right of access**  
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller free information about his or her personal data stored at any time and a copy of this information. 

Furthermore, the Information Technology Act, 2000 in India and the European directives and regulations grant the data subject shall have access to the following information:

  * the purposes of the processing of the personal data; 
  * the categories of personal data concerned; 
  * the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed, in particular recipients in third countries or international organisations; 
  * where possible, the envisaged period for which the personal data will be stored, or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period; 
  * the existence of the right to request from the controller rectification of personal data. 

In addition to the above, the European directives and regulations grant the data subject shall have access to the following information 

  * the existence of the right to request from the controller erasure of personal data or restriction of processing of personal data concerning the data subject, or to object to such processing; 
  * the existence of the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority; 
  * where the personal data are not collected from the data subject, any available information as to their source; 
  * the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, referred to in Article 22(1) and (4) of the GDPR and, at least in those cases, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and envisaged consequences of such processing for the data subject.

Furthermore, the data subject shall have a right to obtain information as to whether personal data are transferred to a third country or to an international organisation. Where this is the case, the data subject shall have the right to be informed of the appropriate safeguards relating to the transfer.

If a data subject wishes to avail himself of this right of access, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.

**c) Right to rectification**  
Each data subject shall have the right to obtain from the controller without undue delay the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning him or her. Taking into account the purposes of the processing, the data subject shall have the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement. If a data subject wishes to exercise this right to rectification, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.

**d) Right to erasure (Right to be forgotten)**  
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller the erasure of personal data concerning him or her without undue delay, and the controller shall have the obligation to erase personal data without undue delay where one of the following grounds applies, as long as the processing is not necessary:

  * The personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed. 
  * The data subject withdraws consent to which the processing is based according to point (a) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR, or point (a) of Article 9(2) of the GDPR, and where there is no other legal ground for the processing. 
  * The data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21(1) of the GDPR and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing, or the data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21(2) of the GDPR. 
  * The personal data have been unlawfully processed. 
  * The personal data must be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject. 
  * The personal data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society services referred to in Article 8(1) of the GDPR. 
  * If one of the aforementioned reasons applies, and a data subject wishes to request the erasure of personal data stored by the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd., he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller. An employee of AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. shall promptly ensure that the erasure request is complied with immediately.

Where the controller has made personal data public and is obliged pursuant to Article 17(1) to erase the personal data, the controller, taking account of available technology and the cost of implementation, shall take reasonable steps, including technical measures, to inform other controllers processing the personal data that the data subject has requested erasure by such controllers of any links to, or copy or replication of, those personal data, as far as processing is not required. Anemployee of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. will arrange the necessary measures in individual cases.

**e) Right of restriction of processing**  
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller restriction of processing where one of the following applies:

  * The accuracy of the personal data is contested by the data subject, for a period enabling the controller to verify the accuracy of the personal data. 
  * The processing is unlawful and the data subject opposes the erasure of the personal data and requests instead the restriction of their use instead. 
  * The controller no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but they are required by the data subject for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. 
  * The data subject has objected to processing pursuant to Article 21(1) of the GDPR pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of the controller override those of the data subject. 
  * If one of the aforementioned conditions is met, and a data subject wishes to request the restriction of the processing of personal data stored by the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd., he or she may at any time contact any employee of the controller. The employee of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. will arrange the restriction of the processing. 

**f) Right to data portability**  
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator, to receive the personal data concerning him or her, which was provided to a controller, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. He or she shall have the right to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from the controller to which the personal data have been provided, as long as the processing is based on consent pursuant to point (a) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR or point (a) of Article 9(2) of the GDPR, or on a contract pursuant to point (b) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR, and the processing is carried out by automated means, as long as the processing is not necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller.

Furthermore, in exercising his or her right to data portability pursuant to Article 20(1) of the GDPR, the data subject shall have the right to have personal data transmitted directly from one controller to another, where technically feasible and when doing so does not adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.

In order to assert the right to data portability, the data subject may at any time contact any employee of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd..

**g) Right to object**  
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to object, on grounds relating to his or her particular situation, at any time, to processing of personal data concerning him or her, which is based on point (e) or (f) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR. This also applies to profiling based on these provisions.

The AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. shall no longer process the personal data in the event of the objection, unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override the interests, rights and freedoms of the data subject, or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

If the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. processes personal data for direct marketing purposes, the data subject shall have the right to object at any time to processing of personal data concerning him or her for such marketing. This applies to profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing. If the data subject objects to the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. to the processing for direct marketing purposes, the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. will no longer process the personal data for these purposes.

In addition, the data subject has the right, on grounds relating to his or her particular situation, to object to processing of personal data concerning him or her by the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. for scientific or historical research purposes, or for statistical purposes pursuant to Article 89(1) of the GDPR, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.

In order to exercise the right to object, the data subject may contact any employee of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. In addition, the data subject is free in the context of the use of information society services, and notwithstanding Directive 2002/58/EC, to use his or her right to object by automated means using technical specifications.

**h) Automated individual decision-making, including profiling**  
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning him or her, or similarly significantly affects him or her, as long as the decision (1) is not necessary for entering into, or the performance of, a contract between the data subject and a data controller, or (2) is not authorised by Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject and which also lays down suitable measures to safeguard the data subject’s rights and freedoms and legitimate interests, or (3) is not based on the data subject’s explicit consent.

If the decision (1) is necessary for entering into, or the performance of, a contract between the data subject and a data controller, or (2) it is based on the data subject’s explicit consent, the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd. shall implement suitable measures to safeguard the data subject’s rights and freedoms and legitimate interests, at least the right to obtain human intervention on the part of the controller, to express his or her point of view and contest the decision.

If the data subject wishes to exercise the rights concerning automated individual decision-making, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd..

**i) Right to withdraw data protection consent**  
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to withdraw his or her consent to processing of his or her personal data at any time.

If the data subject wishes to exercise the right to withdraw the consent, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the AglaSem EduTech Pvt. Ltd..

**j) Data Retention**

We keep most of your personal data for as long as your account is open.We retain your personal data while your account is in existence or as needed to provide you Services. This includes data you or others provided to us and data generated or inferred from your use of our Services. Even if you only use our Services when looking for new courses, admissions, a new job every few years, we will retain your information and keep your profile open until you decide to close your account.

#### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### Closure of Account

If you choose to close your AglaSem account on the Website, if any, your personal data will generally stop being visible to others on our Services within 24 hours. We generally delete closed account information within 30 days of account closure, except as noted below.

We retain your personal data even after you have closed your account if reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations (including law enforcement requests), meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, maintain security, prevent fraud and abuse, enforce our User Agreement, or fulfill your request to “unsubscribe” from further messages from us. We will retain de-personalized information after your account has been closed.

Information you have shared with others (e.g., through email, updates or group posts) will remain visible after you closed your account or deleted the information from your own profile or mailbox, and we do not control data that other data subjects copied out of our Services. 

#### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

#### What rights you have over your data stored due to registration or commenting.

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

#### Security

We implement security safeguards designed to protect your data, such as HTTPS. We regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks. However, we cannot warrant the security of any information that you send us. There is no guarantee that data may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

#### GRIEVANCE OFFICER

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer for data subjects in India is as follows: 

Name: Anand  
Email Id: anand[at]aglasem[dot]com  
Address: 503, Park Centra, Sector 30, Gurgaon, India – 122001

In the event you wish to make a complaint regarding any violation of the provisions of the Privacy Policy, you may send a written complaint to the Grievance Officer, who shall redress the complaint within one (1) month.

#### DATA PROTECTION OFFICER

For Data subjects accessing the Website from the Designated Countries, the details of the Data Protection Officer are as follows: 

Name: Nikhil  
Email Id: nikhil[at]aglasem[dot]com  
Address: 503, Park Centra, Sector 30, Gurgaon, India – 122001

_This Privacy Policy was last updated on 01 Nov, 2018._
